https://www.peakinternet.com/privacy-policy/

This Privacy Policy governs the ways in which Peak Internet (Peak, we or our) collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from our customers, visitors to our websites, and visitors to our customer’s websites (Users). In the course of providing services to Users, whether they are customers, visitors to our website, or visitors to our customer’s websites, we collect information. Each User has a different definition of what information they consider to be private. The purpose of our Privacy Policy is to discuss how we handle the majority of information we collect, or which comes into our possession. Simply because information is discussed in this policy does not mean it is necessarily considered by us to be private. Our Privacy Policy supplements, but does not replace our Terms of Service and Acceptable Use Policy. You may find these policies useful in learning how we handle information. If at any time, you would like to know how specific information is handled, please e-mail us at support@peakinternet.com. How we collect information. Cookies. Our website uses cookies. Cookies are small data files that are placed automatically on a User’s computer by our computers. These data files are read by our computer to determine whether you have visited our site before, how often, the length of time and which pages you view. Registration, Billing and Customer Records. When Users become customers they provide us with their name, address, phone number, user name, credit/debit card or bank information and other personally identifiable or confidential information. This information may be aggregated to create an administrative record that includes information related to the products and services provided to you, how you use those services, problems related to the services, and notations from our staff about our relationship with you, among other things (collectively, Registration and Billing Information). Customer Inquiries. If you contact us about a problem or with a question we may ask you for specific information related to the reason you have contacted us (Customer Inquiry Information). This information may be tied or input into your Registration or Billing Information. Statistical Information. All of our servers collect statistical information such as your IP address, date you visited, computer you are using, and operating system, among other data (Statistical Information). Third Party Products and Services. We offer products and services that are provided by third parties (Third Party Products). These Third Party Products may collect and use information in ways that differ from those set out in this Privacy Policy. Links to the websites of providers of Third Party Products are set out on the Product Description Page (referred to in our Terms of Service). PEAKZone PEAK INTERNET collects and processes information provided directly by you when you install the App and register for an account to use the App. Specifically, this information includes: •Your name, email address, location, user’s phone or contact book data, user’s inventory of installed apps, and user’s screen recording;
•Browser information and session cookies related to your access and use of the App;
•Data insights PEAK INTERNET attains based on correlation and analytics of your information collected in providing the App, which may be used in aggregated and dis-aggregated formats or to obtain trend analytics, to provide the App; and
•Use of the above-described collected information in aggregated and dis-aggregated formats to enhance our current App or to provide App features. How We Use the Information We Collect. General Information. All information either alone, or when combined with other information, may be processed in such a way as to identify Users individually. This section describes how we use various categories of information, and whether we use it, or process it, in ways which can identify a User individually. Cookies. We use the information provided by the cookies to change the way our website looks to you; to keep you logged in to certain areas of the website; and to collect demographic data about where visitors to our website go and how they behave. We do not use this data to identify Users individually. Registration and Billing Information. We use Registration and Billing Information to identify Users individually. Registration and Billing Information is used throughout our business to provide services to you, and to market new Peak products and services to you. Information related to payment, such as a User’s credit card number, is only used to ensure we receive payment for services rendered. It may be shared with third parties affiliated with us if they provide services through us to you and those services are billed by them independently. Currently, no other Registration and Billing Information is disclosed outsite Peak. Customer Inquiries. We use Customer Inquiry Information to identify Users individually. It is used throughout our business to provide services to you, and to market new Peak products and services to you. Customer Inquiry Information is shared with third parties in the following circumstances: to identify and fix problems with services when we are not capable of doing so ourselves. When Customer Inquiry Information is shared with third parties in this way, the third parties are required to keep this information confidential. Statistical Information. We use statistical information to operate our hardware and software, diagnose problems and administer our website. We may use aggregate information to modify the products and services we offer based on who is visiting our website, and what they are purchasing. We do not use this data to identify Users individually. Other disclosures. Peak is required to comply with relevant laws, regulations and judicial orders. Information covered by this Privacy Policy, as well as other categories of information, may be disclosed to third parties if we determine, in our sole discretion, that such a disclosure is necessary or required. We may also disclose this information if in our sole discretion such a disclosure is necessary or required to protect our interests or the interests of our customers. We may also disclose this information in connection with the sale of our business. PEAKZone PEAK INTERNET uses the information collected as described in this Privacy Policy, including personal information, to: •Provide you with the App as described in the Agreement;
•Implement, improve and/or enhance the App, including to make future releases available to you;
•Carry out PEAK INTERNET obligations as described or authorized in the Agreement and this Privacy Policy;
•Enforce PEAK INTERNET rights arising from the Agreement between you and PEAK INTERNET; and
•Fulfill any other purpose authorized by you and reasonably required for the App. Data Security. The information set out in this Privacy Policy is protected using industry standard security measures. Unless disclosure is authorized as set out above, our employees are required to keep User information confidential. However no means of communication or information transmission or storage is totally secure. We cannot be responsible for loss corruption or unauthorized acquisition and use of information, or for any damages resulting therefrom, including unauthorized acquisition and use. Options and Inquiries. To modify or update your Registration and Billing Information please contact us via telephone at one of the numbers listed on our website, www.peakinternet.com
